traditionaloven.com 2018-03-11

# Privacy Policy - traditionaloven.com

## Privacy Policy for www.traditionaloven.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by **email: pizzapaddle@gmail.com**

At **www.traditionaloven.com** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by **www.traditionaloven.com** and how the information is used. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit and use **www.traditionaloven.com** web site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**   
Cookies make website visits more convenient by improved functionality. Cookies are part of a method of tracking information you enter on a web site using a file on your computer. We do use a cookie to log whether you have visited the site already before. No personal information is written to the cookie at all. It is primarily used to save you time by automatically populating contact forms, forms in our Blog, discussion forum, and other locations on the site.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site:

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.
  * Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * To comply with this disclosure, obligation, with respect to Google's use of data, please read this page: [How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).
  * Users may opt out of Google's personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).
  * Alternatively, users may to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

Our users may visit these website of the third-party vendors, or ad networks serving ads, to opt out of the use of cookies for personalized advertising (if the vendors or ad networks offers this capability). Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of some third-party vendors' uses of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send the advertisements and links that appear on **www.traditionaloven.com** directly to your browsers. These automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you can see.

Please note that **www.traditionaloven.com** privacy practices as described on this page do not apply to the privacy policies or practices of other businesses and websites. **www.traditionaloven.com** has no access to, or control over, these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. These matters are very common to the web and always evolving, but if you wish to learn or just to find out more, please consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **www.traditionaloven.com** privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Site Tracking - Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, **www.traditionaloven.com** makes use of log files. We use **[Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/#?modal_active=none "Google's Analytics program.")** solutions for our statistics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Email Addresses**  
We log your email address in only in these situations: Newsletter purpose, contact/email-reply purpose, when posting comment to a Blog post. The email addresses are never shared with anyone.

**Out-going Links to other websites  
**Our site contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policy and practices or, the content of any other web site linked from **www.traditionaloven.com** site.

Thank you.

In fact you can bake for 4 to 6 hours reloading batches in the oven (including slow long time roasting at baking temperatures.) My favorites are whole mixed grains breads, Sour Dough and Turkish breads, sweets of course. It's a good idea to own a proper book about baking strategies, I ordered this one from eBay and I'm enjoying reading it ever since:

Great as present, or must have DIY Book by Peter Reinhart: "The Bread Baker's Apprentice".

To link to this **Privacy Policy** page from your website, only cut and paste the following code into your web page.   
It will appear on your page as: [Privacy Policy.](http://www.traditionaloven.com/privacy_policy.html "Privacy Policy")
